Preliminary Guide to the Vice President for Student and Academic Support Services records, 1821 ca.-2005 RG0006
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Communication and Creative Services, circa 1983-2000; RG0006 Series 9; no content (Box 5, Box 8, Box 7, Box 6, Box 2, Box 1, Box 4, Box 3)
  - Slides of campus people and events, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Binder of slides: Shot through windows of Mitchell Hall, Male looking out from Mitchell porch, Male on Mitchell porch with Bear, Mitchell Bear, Making cookies in Strong, Mitchell Hall Front TOTAL, Male student studying in his room Mitchell, Students on stage at Mitchell Rec room, Students at RHA Meeting, Kelvin Glover and friends talking on Mitchell Porch, Male student reading on Mitchell porch, Room in Crawford-2students, Campus Scenes
  - Slides of campus people and events, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Binder of slides: Student Life, Quad, Campus, Outdoor student shots, classrooms
  - Slides of campus people and events, 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Binder of slides: Student Life, GW icons, SASS COMM, Parents' Day, Maui Luau, Marvin Gras, Solar Car, Campus, Colonial Inauguration, Residential Life, Sports
  - Slides of campus people and events, 1989-1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Binder of slides: Embassy Dinner, Excellence In Student Life Awards, Golden Key, Graduation, Greek Week: Greek Weekend Senior Night, Greek Weekend Games, God and Goddess Competition, Chariot Races
  - Slides of campus people and events, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Binder of slides: Commencement, G Street shots, Foggy Bottom metro, Inside Marvin Center, Bookstore, Convocation, 2000 Penn., The Early Years, Nostalgia, GW Statue and Landmarks, Residence Hall Move-In, Music, Art, Random/NROTC, MVC, Campus Scenes
  - Slides of campus people and events, 1997-1998 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Binder of slides: Students, Campus Scenes, Midnight Breakfast
  - Slides of campus people and events, 1996-2000 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Binder of slides: Home and Campus, Students, Campus Scenes, Cheerleaders, SASS COMM, CLLC Holiday card, Ronald Reagan, George Bush, Hilary Clinton
  - Slides of campus people and events, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Binder of slides: Presidential Inauguration ball activities of Bill Clinton
  - Slides of campus people and events, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Binder of: Student Life, Campus Scenes, Students in classroom
  - Slides of campus people and events, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Binder of: Athletics (Volley), The Big 2 Do! Art Fest, Back to Schoold Dance, Blood Drive, Career Week, Colonial Cabinet, Colonial Inauguration, Collonade Gallery: International Photographers, Mambo Reflections, Computer Fair, Conference M.C., Dimock Gallery: Lithographic Review
  - Slides of campus people and events, 1989-1993 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Binder of: Spring Fling, Staff-OCL, Christmas/Holiday party, Staff Orientation, Student Life, Student Orientation, Summer Series, Super Dance, Thanksgiving Dinner
  - Slides of campus people and events, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Binder of slides: Students at outdoor classroom behind Monroe Hall, Students on grass at class, Professor teaching, Two Engineer Profs and Student at Computer, Gerald Lee and Accounting Professor, Bookshelves with bust of General Grant, Chemical Flasks with colored liquids, Students at MSSC Lounge, Melvin Brock and Student, Classroom Scenes
  - Slides of campus people and events, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Binder of slides: Historic: 1970s Staff, Views of Campus, Health Services, Staff and Students 1974, 1974 Staff
  - Slides of campus people and events, circa 1965-1991 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Binder of slides: Historic: Bush/Gorbachev Summit (not slides but several black and white photographs and proof sheets), Ronald Reagan (photo), Campus Scenes, Female Students (photographs, ca.1960s).
  - Slides of campus people and events, 1991-1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Binder of slides: Medieval Day, Campus Scenes, Beach-O-Rama, Marvin Gras, Spring Fling, VIVA II
  - Slides of campus people and events, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Binder of slides: campus scenes
  - Slides of campus people and events, 1993-1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Binder of slides: Commemcement excercises
  - Photographs of campus people and events, circa 1960-circa 1970 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Binder of photos: Historic Campus Scenes, Students, Basketball
  - Photographs of campus people and events, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Binder of photos: Black and white photographs of campus scenes, color photographs of special GW events, Student Life, Dorms, Campus Scenes, Fallout Party PB, Students.
  - Slides of campus people and events, 1987-1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Binder of slides: Females talking with flowers backdrop, Female painting on Academic Center roof, Male painting on Acad Center roof, Academic Center, Gelman outside, Posters on glass of Acad Center, Fans at Baseball game, Players at Baseball game, Spring Fling 1992, Water Polo. DJ at WRGW, Female WRGW Manager, Parents' Weekend 1992, Medieval Day 1993, Colonial Inauguration Dinner 1993.
  - Slides of campus people and events, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Admissions Slide Show - Monuments, Campus, Campus Scenes
  - Slides of campus people and events, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Slide Show - Students, Campus Scenes
  - Slides of campus people and events, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Slides of campus people and events, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Admissions Slide Show - Students, Campus Scenes
  - Slides of campus people and events, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Binder of slides: Greek Life, Athletics, Students, Residence Hall Life
  - Slides of campus people and events, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Binder of slides: Gelman, Academic Center, Alumni House, Corcoran, Funger, Hillel, Bldg HH, Lisner Hall, Lisner Auditorium, Marvin Center, Samson, Rice Hall, Monroe, Hall of Government, Smith Center, Woodhull House, Law School, Medical School, Hospital, Residence Halls
    Classroom photos: Donna Scarboro with students (some individual photos of students), Lillien Robinson/National Gallery, female student scuplting, theater class in Lisner auditorium: Alan Wade-summer class, engineering classroom with student in grey/white striped shirt and woman in white t-shirt and glasses, Hammerman class outside in Monroe Rose Gardens with female student at podium, students in front of computers, student with goggles working in chemistry lab, pensive male student in class, engineering machines with fog.
    Students Studying: basketball player (Sonni Holland) studying in Guthridge Hall lounge, Natsuko Amito in yellow sweathshirt, female student in blue shirt reading book in Marvin Center, female student with long curly hari in plum shirt reading book, Luyi in Gelman library sitting between green bookshelves.
  - Slides of campus people and events, 1995-1998 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Binder of slides: Mount Vernon Campus: Campus Scenes, Basketball, Students, Summer Getaway Ropes Course
  - Slides of campus people and events, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Binder of slides: Colonial Inauguration, U.S.-Soviet Union Summit, Homecoming Crowning, Greek Competitions in Smith Center, Homecoming Talent Show (Pike and Sigma Kappa Dance), Homecoming Parade, Greeks at Basketball game (Homecoming), basketball coaches of men's and women's teams, Troubadours.
  - Photos: President Clinton with Mike Jarvis, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Photos: Campus Scenes, circa 1960-circa 1970 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Photos: Campus Scenes, circa 1980-circa 1990 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Photos: Campus Scenes, circa 1990 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Photos: Campus Scenes, circa 1995 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Photos: Engineering Students, circa 1995 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Photos: GW Students at White House, circa 1995 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Photos: Mount Vernon Campus Olympic Torch Run, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Photos: Students at Washington rowing club, circa 1995 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Photos: Students in dorms, circa 1995 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Photos: SOS Barbeque, circa 1990 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Photos: University Police, circa 1980-circa 1990 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Photos: Fallout Party, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Photos: Excellence in Student Life Awards, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Photos: Excellence in Student Life Awards, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Photos: Opening Convocation, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Photos: Excellence in Student Life Awards, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Photos: Marvin Center dining services, circa 1980 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Photos: Commencement, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Photos: Ronald Reagan, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Photos: Student Protests-South Africa, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Photos: President Trachtenberg, undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Photos: Marvin Center, circa 1980 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Photos: Firehouse, circa 1980 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Men's uniform top, circa 2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Cheerleader uniform top, small "GW" lettering in blue and gold against white top, with blue, gold, white design on bottom. Acc#27.025
  - Men's uniform top, circa 2000 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Cheerleader uniform top, "Colonials" in blue lettering bordered by gold and blue. Acc#27.025
  - Men's uniform top, circa 2000 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Cheerleader uniform top, large "GW" with blue lettering on buff, lower half and back of uniform are blue. Acc#27.025
  - Women's uniform top and skirt, circa 2000 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Cheerleader uniform top and skirt, "Colonials" in blue lettering bordered in gold and white, with blue skirt. Acc#27.025
  - Women's uniform top and skirt, circa 2000 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Cheerleader uniform top and skirt, "GW" lettering on buff top, with blue skirt. Acc#27.025
  - Women's uniform top and skirt, circa 2000 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    Cheerleader uniform top and skirt, "Colonials" gold lettering on white background and blue top, with blue skirt. Acc#27.025
  - Men's uniform top, circa 2000 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Cheerleader uniform top, large "GW" logo with blue lettering on gold with white background. Gold front and back. Acc#27.025
- Student Activities Center, 01/13/2009; Series 10; George Washington University. Student Activities Center; 0.25 Linear Feet 1 Box; .25 linear feet (Box 1)
  - Student Organization Fair, January 13, 2009, 01/13/2009; Series 10 Box 9; 0.25 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Summary
    Contains flyers and brochures handed out during Student Organization Fair, January 13, 2009. The Student Organization Fair is hosted during Welcome Back Week by the Student Activities Center, a department of the Student and Academic Support Services.
    Student organizations represented: Latinas Promoviendo Comunidad/Lambda Pi Chi Soririty; Sigma Psi Theta Sorority; George Washington University Bands; Alpha Chi Sigma; GW Trails; Student Global AIDS Campaign; Parents Families and Friends of Lesbians and Gays (PFLAG); Camp Kesem; GW Students for Fairtrade; Fourteenth Grade Players; Students Defending Democracy; Liebertad para Oscar Elias Biscet; College Republicans; Black Student Union; AKPSI; GW Business Leaders Corp.; Multicultural Student Services Center; National Society of Black Engineers (NSBE); Circle K International; JKA Karate Club of GWU; Multicultural Greek Council; Alpha Kappa Alpha Sorority; Green GW; Genocide Intervention Network; La Unidad Latina; Delta Phi Epsilon; Phi Alpha Delta; Alpha Kappa Psi; Mount Vernon Campus; GW Independent Arts Collective; GW Sailing; Trans Education and Action (TEA); Phi Alpha Theta; Purple Ribbon Campaign; Multicultural Business Student Association; Roosevelt Institution; Turning the Page GW; GW Ballroom; International Affairs Society; College Democrats; William F. Buckley Society
- Student Support and Family Engagement photographs, newsletters and DVDs, 1991-2011; Series 11; 4.5 Linear Feet 3 record center cartons (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3)
  This series contains photographs of students, parents, families and events including meetings of the Parents Association Advisory Council, Colonial Inauguration (CI), move-in, and family weekend. DVD recordings of Colonial Inauguration (1991, 1993, 1995-2002, 2009-2011). Copies of the Colonial Parents' Connection newsletter (1993-2002). Parents' Association branded weekly planners (2009). Also included one copy of the 2011 Cherry Tree.
  - Albums and contact sheets (Box 1)
  - Contact sheets, negatives and prints, 1991-1996 (Box 2)
  - Prints, newsletters, dvds and weekly planners (Box 3)